

Thuratun

Web Developer

- No(46).157 Street, Tamwe, Yangon. # 13/12/1996 Burmese
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/thuya-tun-594044204/

PROFILE

Hi! My name is Thura Tun. I am a Junior Web Developer, and I'm here to introduce myself in my professional portfolio. I hope that you enjoy the work I've created. I've been working in CB bank PCL for 4.7 years, Mynamar ICT Solution for 1 years and I've had the privilege of working with some fantastic clients. I'm excited to be able to share my work with you here. If you have any questions, feel free to reach out to me at thuratundev@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

2022 – 01/2024 Yangon, Myanmar

Myanmar ICT Solution (MISL)

Junior Web Develoepr

I'm a Junior Web Developer. For the past one year, I've been working on projects for internship, including e-commerce, Travel-blog, Governance, Qr Generation, cryptocurrency non-profits and other projects. I love creating engaging user experiences that are both functional and engaging.

01/2024 – present Yangon, Myanmar

Myanmar ICT Solution (MISL)

Mid Level Developer

Hi! My name is Thura Tun. I am a mid level Developer, and I'm here to introduce myself in my professional portfolio. I hope that you enjoy the work I've created. I've been working in MISL(myanmarictsolutions) for 1 years, and I've had the privilege of working with some fantastic clients. I'm excited to be able to share my work with you here. If you have any questions, feel free to reach out to me at thuratundev@gmail.com

EDUCATION

01/2013 – 01/2017 Yangon, Myanmar **Bsc (Physics)**Dagon University ♂

CERTIFICATES

- Fullstack Developer Course
- Information Technology
- Banking Training

SKILLS

- HTML
- Bootstrap
- Json
- React
- Git & Git Hub
- codeigniter

- CSS
- Jquery
- Php
- Restful API
- Cpanel

- Javascript
- Ajax
- Laravel
- MySQL
- Digital Ocean

</> FINISHED PROJECTS

Laravel PizzaOrderSystem project

POS

Laravel PizzaOrderSystem project (Laravel pizza order system with admin panel and user panel What admin can do Create, edit or delete category Create, edit or delete pizza products Manage order lists from users Change user accounts to admin and vice versa Delete accounts Check feedback from users Update own profile and password What user can do Search pizza products or check products detail Add products to cart and manage cart Order products to admin Send feedback to admin Update own profile and password Languages and Packages Bootstrap and Blade for UI jQuery for dynamic UI and functions Laravel Jetstream for authentication MySQL for database)

My Portfolio project

Portfolio

My Portfolio project (Portfolio bootstrap project with introduce myself and my finished project. This project contain detail of about me. Language contain HTML, CSS, Bootstrap)

JavaScript Calculator Project

Calculator

JavaScript Calculator Project (Calculator project can calculate and sum, minus, divided, Multiply. Languages contain HTML, CSS, JavaScript)

PHP Travel Blog

PHP (Pure)

PHP Travel Blog (PHP travel blog project with frontend and backend panel. What project can do Create, Read, Edit or delete users accounts and links frontend Posts. This project contains HTML, CSS, Javascript, PHP, MySQL)

Coin Bank Kr

Cryptocurrency

Coin Bank Kr (This project have frontend is React Js and backend is Laravel). This project is created me and my team.

MMQrCodeGenerator

qrgenerator

MMQrCodeGenerator(MMQrCodeGenerator project with Learning Page, frontend and backend admin-panel. What

project can do? Admin can create share admin and create ticket for user and other doing more action. Ticket can contact

user and admin. User can create 2 types of QR Code. 2 types of QR codes have static QR and Dynamic QR. Static QR

have URL, Vcard, Text, SMS, E-mail, Phone, Wifi can generate QR Code.Dynamic QR is more interesting it has 2 types of

industry. There is Restaurant, Personal, Pagoda. Restaurant have 4 template PDF, Bussiness Page, Menu and Website.Personal have 1 template PDF. Pagoda have 1 template PDF. It can be do custom color and information

Template have 2 types of designs Frame and Template. Frame have more custom color QR code and Frame design can

add logo with QR Code. Template have 1 design but it can be do custom color template with Logo. Some Other function is

in progress .(This project have contains HTML,CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, PHP, Laravel and Other packages.) OTP code servie and payment gateway(K-pay)

MMChatAI

Myanmar Chat GPT AI

MMChatAI (Myanmar Chat GPT AI project with frontend and backend admin-panel. What project can do? Admin can

create share admin and add advertise custom advertisement share permission. User can ask questions and change user

This resume is made with Jobseeker.com.

password.(This project contains HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Laravel, Bootstrap, Chat GPT API and other packages.)

React Weather App

React Weather App API

React weather app is showing real Temperature, Country, Humidity, Visibility and local time. It can search country showing real temperature.

• ON GOING PROJECTS

PSH

Setra Digital Weighing Scale

This project has admin and user. Admin can manage website information and discuss user complaints. Admin can display product information and details etc

	LAN	GUAGES	
English	• • • • •		
S COMMUNICATION SKILL			
Team Work Excellent	• • • •	Interpersonal skills Excellent	• • • •
Good Learning Skills Excellent	• • • •	Problem solving Skills Excellent	• • • •
Creative idea Excellent	• • • •	Self-study Excellent	• • • • •